Nguyen Du Lap

BACKEND DEVELOPER (INTERNS)



Contact information

- 22/01/2002
- 0867415853
- ndl22012002@gmail.com
- https://github.com/MuleupNguyen
- Quan 9, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

Skills

Back - end

- Javascript, Java, C#
- Node.JS(Express), Spring Boot, ASP.NET

Front - end

- HTML, CSS(SCSS), Javascript
- jQuery, Bootstrap 4, 5, React.JS

Languages

· Basic English skills

Interest

- · Sports: Badminton, soccer, swimming...
- · Reading stories, team building...
- Coding

Career Objective

I am currently studying information technology at Nong Lam University. I have participated in a number of projects and research in the Website field. I hope to join a position of the company to apply the knowledge learned to work.

When working as a developer, I will bring the knowledge and skills I learned in studying to solve tasks. During my work, I will always try to accumulate experience and improve my knowledge to become a good developer.

Education

Nong Lam University in Ho Chi Minh City

9/2020 - Now

Information technology

4th year student

Work experience

Website selling books

1/2023 - 6/2023

Build a website to sell books

- · Link github: https://github.com/Nguyen-Du-Lap/book-selling-website
- Link demo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kY47jHJI5ic&;t=29s
- · Number of members: 02, source code management with github
- Building technology:
- + Front-end: HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT(JSP, JSTL)
- + Back-end: Java(Servlet)
- · Main function description:
- + CRUD user, staff, product, order....(Upload product images, load data from MySQL)
 - + Calculate delivery fee, arrival time (using express delivery API)
 - + Export file excel, pdf
 - + Log system
 - + Shopping cart, product reviews, comments
- + Register, log in, forgot password (register, log in with email, google, facebook)
 - + Customer support ...

Website selling tours

4/2023 - Now

Build a website to sell domestic and foreign tours

- Link github: https://github.com/MuleupNguyen/front-end-travel
- Link demo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q6LJ95AQqIQ
- · Number of members: 03, source code management with github
- · Building technology:
- +Front-end: HTML, CSS(SCSS), JAVASCRIPT, REACT.JS, REDUX
- +Back-end: JAVASCRIPT, JSON-SERVER
- · Main function description:
- + Register, log in
- + Search and arrange tours
- + Pay
- + Rate comment feedback